# Daniel Arbon

Phone: **0422 735 715** Email: danieltarbon@live.com.au Location: Hallett Cove, South Australia, Australia 5158

GitHub: https://github.com/arbdt

Portfolio: <a href="https://arbdt.github.io/responsive-portfolio/">https://arbdt.github.io/responsive-portfolio/</a> LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/daniel-arbon-9bbb2419a/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/daniel-arbon-9bbb2419a/</a>

#### **SUMMARY**

A web developer with experience creating both front-end and back-end, and a certificate in Full Stack Web Development. Experience includes generating HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, using AJAX-based API calls, creating server applications with Express, using MySQL databases, and using Git and GitHub for version control. Also experienced with teamwork and customer/client interaction.

#### **PROJECTS**

# **International Space Station Tracker**

Repo: <a href="https://github.com/arbdt/bcs-project-1">https://github.com/arbdt/bcs-project-1</a> Live: <a href="https://arbdt.github.io/bcs-project-1/">https://arbdt.github.io/bcs-project-1/</a> HTML, CSS, JS

- Co-developer in group of two
- A website that makes use of JSON from APIs to display International Space Station data
- Ajax, Semantic UI, Google Maps
- Worked on Ajax API calls to retrieve and display data

# **Coffee Rater**

Repo: <a href="https://github.com/dcon0610/Project2">https://github.com/dcon0610/Project2</a>

Live: <a href="https://salty-forest-45628.herokuapp.com/">https://salty-forest-45628.herokuapp.com/</a>

HTML, CSS, JS

- Co-developer in three-person team
- A website that allows users to upload information about coffees to a database, and also attach reviews to those coffees
- Makes use of Express, Handlebars, Ajax, Sequelize, MySQL, Bootstrap
- Created front end using Handlebars with Bootstrap, and utilised JQuery with Ajax for client-side scripting

## **Javascript Code Quiz**

Repo: https://github.com/arbdt/code-quiz
Live: https://arbdt.github.io/code-quiz/

### HTML, CSS, JS

- Solo project
- A website that delivers a short five-question quiz about JavaScript
- Uses JQuery, Local Storage

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Web development with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Mobile Application development with Java and Swift
- Programming in Java, Python, C++, C#, and ASP.net
- Proficiency with JQuery, Bootstrap, Ajax, Express, MySQL
- Proficient with Microsoft Windows and Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Powerpoint)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**Volunteer,** Resthaven Onkaparinga Community Services, Noarlunga Centre SA 2020 - present

Assisting a community organisation with running a ten pin bowling activity for a mens' group. Duties include helping to collect bowling equipment (hire shoes, bowling balls, bowling aids), taking orders for and distributing refreshments, and assisting with participant mobility.

# Technical Support, Self-employed, Adelaide SA

2015 - present

Providing technical support and advice by phone or in-person, for Windows PC, Apple IOS and Android devices. Tasks have included setting up new hardware, installing or troubleshooting software, maintaining printers and home networks.

**Research Assistant,** Torrens Resilience Institute, Adelaide SA 2012 - 2013

Assisted with collecting data on topics of interest to the organisation. Wrote reports related to that data for the organisation. Assisted with assembling and posting information packages to potential clients.

**Administration Assistant (contractual),** Torrens Resilience Institute, Adelaide SA 2012

Briefly filled in for administrator/receptionist while they were on break. Duties included locking and unlocking the office, signing off on received goods and

documents, generating PDF files for staff, answering telephone or in-person enquiries.

Refill Assistant, Big W Marion, Oaklands Park SA

2008 - 2009

Tidied and restocked shelves. Directed customers to aisles containing products they were interested in, or to departments better able to help them. Answered telephone enquiries.

#### **EDUCATION**

Full Stack Web Development Boot Camp Certificate, University of Adelaide 2020 - 2021

- 24 week course on full-stack web-development.
- Subjects included HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax APIs, Node.js, Express, MySQL, Mongo, React

# Bachelor of Information Technology, University of South Australia

2016 - 2018

- Majors: Mobile App Development, Software Development
- Subjects included: Java, C++, .Net, Unix, Visual Studio, Project Management (PRINCE2 framework), System Analysis and Design, Interface Design, Data Structures, Android Studio, XCode, Swift

**Diploma of Information Technology**, South Australian Institute of Business and Technology

2015 - 2015

• Subjects included: Python, Java, IT Fundamentals, Network Fundamentals

#### Bachelor of Nursing, Flinders University

2013 - 2014

• Included 2 placements at major metropolitan hospitals

# **Graduate Diploma in Plant Health and Biosecurity**, University of Adelaide

2011 - 2011

**Bachelor of Science**, Flinders University

2007 - 2010

• Majors: Molecular Biology, Microbiology